Please set me free,
and just let me be
Cause all these policies and
all this corporate greed
It really gets to me
so please set me free, and just let me be
Cause all these policies and
all this corporate greed
It really gets to me,
so please set me free
Cause my people in chains
we ain't diggin' through the couch
but what we seekin’ is change
Cause we done been through hell
and I been peepin' the flames
All these crooked politicians,
they the people to blame
So please set me free,
and just let me live
Y'all done took so much,
got nothin’ left to give
Wait I take that back,
what I got left’s a fist
And I'ma use it to write,
so just accept this gift
So please set me free, leave my city alone
This is BPT, I call this city my
home! We all kings and queens,
just wanna sit on my throne
But we ain't gettin' no loans, we
gotta get it alone So please set
me free, and just let me be great
Now you movin' into town, and we ain't
gettin' no say With all this
gentrification, we ain't gettin' to stay
See, y'all been eatin' off of us, and
we ain't gettin' a plate So please
set me free, and just let me be
Cause all these policies, and all
this corporate greed It really
gets to me, so please set me free
And just let me be, cause all these
policies And all this corporate
greed, it really gets to me
So please set me free, I just wanna
live life A diamond watch would be
nice, but I ain't rockin' with ice
And all this talk about these monopoles
just isn't right This isn't what God
meant when he said, let there be light
So please set me free, stop
holdin' me back There's a war
outside, my people under attack
The government don't care about us,
I've accepted the fact Cause y'all was
settin a trap, now we all set in a trap
So please set me free, cause I don't
wanna be here Me, it's not what you
rulin', I just wanna be clear
All this anti-immigration, got my
cousins in fear My fist is up in the
air, cause the freedom up in the air
So please set me free, it's been
way too long Can't wait for the
day I ain't gotta sing this song
Can't wait for the day that you goin'
right to wrong But who we kiddin', I'll
be waitin' till the day that I'm gone
So please set me free, and just let me be
Cause all these policies, and all this
corporate greed It really gets to me
So please set me free, and just let me be
Cause all these policies, and all this
corporate greed It really gets to me
So please set me free, and just let me be
Cause all these policies, and all this
corporate greed It really gets to me
So please set me free, and just let me be
Cause all these policies, and all this
corporate greed It really gets to me
So please set me free